thecheesecakefactory.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 25, 2018

This policy describes how we may collect and use information provided to us by people visiting this website. Because this policy may be revised from time to time, we suggest that you check here periodically for policy updates. "We," "us," "our" and "The Cheesecake Factory" refers collectively to The Cheesecake Factory Incorporated, its subsidiaries and affiliates.

**OUR INFORMATION VALUES**

If you provide us with information about yourself or your company, we believe that you have the right to know why we are collecting that information and how we use it. If, for any reason, you want to opt out of the marketing use of your information, we have an obligation to comply with your request.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

This policy outlines how we obtain your information, what we use it for, and who we share it with, including information you give us, information we collect from you automatically, and information we collect from other sources.

**Information You Give Us**

"Personal information" includes any information identifiable in nature, and may include: your company information, your name, your address, your e-mail, and your employment related information (such as a resume or references). You may visit and use this website without providing Personal Information. We will collect Personal Information only if you provide it to us. If you do not want us to have your Personal Information, please do not provide it to us.

You may provide us with Personal Information through various methods, including (without limitation):

Registration Forms \- If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion, to become a registered user of this website, or to receive information about The Cheesecake Factory, you may be required to fill out a registration form. This form requires that you provide certain Personal Information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, areas of interest, product usage, and/or a unique individual password.

Email and other voluntary communications \- You may also choose to communicate with us through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.

Employment Related Information \- We may retain Personal Information you submit because you are interested in a career with us. We may use the information we collect about you in a variety of ways, including: to process your application; to communicate with you; to conduct applicant and employment-related statistical evaluation and record keeping; to perform aggregated analytics to improve the applicant experience; to respond to your inquiries and requests for information; to maintain and improve our sites; to detect, prevent, or investigate security breaches or fraud; and to maintain appropriate records for internal administrative purposes.

Promotional Communication \- You can opt out of receiving promotional emails and mailings by informing us of your preference at the time you sign up for an account, modifying your promotional preferences online in your account’s profile management section, or following the opt out instructions in the promotional emails we send you. Similarly, you may opt in to receive text messages, telephone calls, and mailings. Where our mobile applications allow for the delivery of “push notifications," you can also opt out of receiving these notifications by toggling the “Notifications" switches within our mobile applications to "off." By downloading and using our mobile application, you may receive promotional messages, offers, news, and information about The Cheesecake Factory or our affiliates within the mobile application itself. These “in app" messages are part of our mobile application’s functionality and cannot be turned off. If you do not want to receive “in app" messages, offers, news, and information, do not download or use our mobile application.

Please note that if you opt out of receiving promotional communications from us, we may still send you transactional communications, including emails about your accounts or purchases.

**Information We Collect Automatically**

Location Information \- When you use a smart phone or other mobile device to access the website, use a computer to access our website, or use our mobile application, we may collect information about your physical location.

Transactions and Activity \- If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through this website, we may collect information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and your other activity on the website. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the website that you visit, transaction types, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amounts, payment, and billing information as well as the nature, quantity and price of the goods or services you exchange and the individuals or entities with whom you communicate or transact business.

Device and Usage Information \- When you visit our website, we automatically collect data about the type of browser you are using, your domain name (the name of your internet service provider, or your company name), your internet protocol (IP) address, the time and length of your visit, the pages you view and the order in which you view them, and the site you last visited before coming to thecheesecakefactory.com. We use this information only to improve our site's content and structure. You will remain anonymous to us unless you provide us with your Personal Information.

Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technology \- We may also employ the use of "cookie" or “beacon” technologies. A "cookie" is a small file that we may place on your hard drive to identify you when you visit our website. A “beacon”, sometimes called a “pixel”, may be embedded on our webpage to communicate certain information from your device to us or a third party. We use these technologies to help analyze our website’s performance and content, track visitor usage, provide you are more customized browsing experience, and determine your eligibility to use certain products or services and to tailor advertisements to you. You may set your browser to refuse the "cookie," but there may be pages on our site you will not be able to access if you do.

**Information We Collect from Other Sources**

Publicly Available Information \- We collect information that is publicly available. For example, we may collect information you submit to a blog, a chat room, or a social network like Facebook, Twitter, or Google+. We may also collect information about you from other companies and organizations. By gathering additional information about you, we can correct inaccurate information and give you product recommendations and special offers that are more likely to interest you.

In-Store Camera Information – We use cameras in stores to keep employees and customers safe and to look for ways to improve our customers’ experiences. We do not use these cameras to identify people except when necessary for security reasons.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

Except for employment related information, which we will use only for purposes related to your potential employment with us, we may use Personal Information for various purposes, including (without limitation): helping to establish and verify the identity of website users; opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users' accounts or memberships; processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications; providing services and support to website users; improving the website, including tailoring it to users' preferences; providing users with product or service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about The Cheesecake Factory; responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions; maintaining the security and integrity of our systems.

We may engage other companies to perform a variety of functions, such as to fulfill orders, assist with promotions, provide technical assistance, customize or personalize the advertisements that are displayed to you, and for other legitimate business purposes (collectively, "Third Parties"). We may share your information with these Third Parties and these Third Parties may use your information only to the extent necessary to fulfill their functions, and for no other purpose. Except as otherwise stated herein, we will not make your information available to any unrelated business or activity for any reason.

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or other legal request, to protect the integrity of the website, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or any other investigation related to public safety.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

Third Parties may collect information—including automatically collected information when you use our website or mobile application(s)—through the methods described in the “Information We Collect” Section above (see “cookie, web beacons, and similar technology”). They also may possess or obtain information about you from your interactions: directly with the third party companies; with other websites, mobile applications, or companies that the Third Parties work with; or from your interactions with advertisements Third Parties display to you.

Marketing partners and other third parties also may collect information about your activity on our sites and on third-party sites using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these third parties is used to decide which ads you see on third-party sites and applications. You may choose not to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers by visiting the following websites: U.S. visitors click here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp/.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp/). Canadian visitors click here: <http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising> and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp/>.

We may also use third party social platforms such as Facebook to provide users customized advertisements. In this instance, a user’s email address, telephone number or other contact information provided to The Cheesecake Factory is converted into a unique value which can be matched to the users social media profile, if they provided that information to the social media platform, such as Facebook. You can visit Facebook for more information on Facebook’s advertising privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. To opt-out of customized social media ads, adjust your social advertising settings (for example, through the settings of your Facebook profile), or use the links provided in the ad itself.  
We may also collect aggregated data, which is data from which the identity of an individual cannot be determined. We may use aggregated data at our discretion.

**DO NOT TRACK NOTICE**

Some browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Our website may contain links to third party websites, such as delivery services and social media pages. These links are intended for your convenience only. These third party websites and services are not related with The Cheesecake Factory and may have separate privacy policies and data collection practices. We have no responsibility for these websites or their privacy practices. We encourage users to read the privacy policies of all websites they visit.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Residents of The State of California may request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Attn: Privacy Officer, The Cheesecake Factory Incorporated, 26901 Malibu Hills Road, Calabasas Hills, CA 91301. In your request, please specify that you want a "The Cheesecake Factory’s California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

This website is directed toward and designed for use only by persons aged 13 or older. We will not approve applications from or establish or maintain registrations for any child we know to be under the age of 13. The Cheesecake Factory does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that we obtained personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is (or who we know to be) under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems.

**SECURITY**

This website employs commercial firewall technology that uses Secure Socket Layer protection and 128-bit encryption to maintain the security of your information. We may assign you a login identification name and password to access our services. We will not disclose such identifying information to any individual without your authorization. The Cheesecake Factory protects your information using commercially reasonable technical, physical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of your information. Some of our safeguards include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls, and administrative informational controls. While we have employed security technologies and procedures to assist safeguarding your personal information, no system or network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If required by law, we shall notify you in the event that any of your Personal Information or other information you provided is compromised.

**DATA PROCESSING AND STORING**

The Cheesecake Factory and its third-party service providers may process or store your personal information in the United States of America, Canada, and/or other countries around the world. Regardless of the company or person who processes your information and where it is processed, we will take steps to protect your information in accordance with applicable data protection laws and this Privacy Policy. We protect your information using technical, physical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of your information and have required our service providers to use similar standards and procedures. While both The Cheesecake Factory and our service providers have employed security technologies and procedures to assist safeguarding your personal information, no system or network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**CHOICE AND CONTROL**

In order to provide service to you, we may send you communications related to your transactions, security, or the administration of this website. From time to time, we may also send you other messages or updates about The Cheesecake Factory, our website, and promotions or other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from The Cheesecake Factory, you may opt-out by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the communication or contact us where specified in the “Contact Us” section, below.  
You may also update information about your account with us. We will update and correct your profile if you wish to make changes.  
Please note that if you opt out of receiving communications from us, we may still send you service communications such as emails about your account or the status of your application.

**ACCESSING YOUR INFORMATION**

Under the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”) of Canada and related Canadian provincial legislation and the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) of the European Union, you have the right, under certain circumstances, to access information we hold about you, including a copy of your customer profile. Under the GDPR of the European Union, you also have the right, under certain circumstances, to request that the data we have collected from you be erased or for your data not to be shared with third parties. Any such requests must be in writing and provided to us at the email or postal address described in the "Contact Us" section below. Any such requests may be subject to a small administrative fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**CONTACT US**

We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about privacy. You may use Contact Us to ask The Cheesecake Factory a privacy question or correct Personal Information or other information you have provided to us. You can contact The Cheesecake Factory’s Privacy Officer at: The Cheesecake Factory Incorporated, 26901 Malibu Hills Road, Calabasas Hills, CA 91301 or via email at [PrivacyOfficer@thecheesecakefactory.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@thecheesecakefactory.com).

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

We may make changes to this policy, and may apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. When we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by posting the updated policy on our website, and we will update the effective date at the end of this policy.
